I'm your new babysitter
Emelie is a horror, thriller film directed by Michael Thelin.
After their regular babysitter cancels, the Thompson family turns to her friend, Anna to
supervise their children while the parents go out to celebrate their anniversary.
At first Anna seems like a dream come true to the kids, allowing them to eat extra cookies and play with things that are usually off-limits, but as her
behaviour becomes increasingly odd, the kids soon find out that her intentions are dark and twisted—and she is not who she seems to be.
Emelie, played by Sarah Bolger.
Joyce Thompson, played by Susan Pourfar.
Dan, played by Chris Beetem.
Jacob, played by Joshua Rush.
Christopher, played by Thomas Bair.
Sally, played by Carly Adams.
Emelie is a 2015 American horror thriller film directed by Michael
Thelin and written by Richard Raymond Harry Herbeck.
The film stars Sarah Bolger, Joshua Rush, Carly Adams,
Thomas Bair, Susan Pourfar and Chris Beetem.
The film was released on March 4, 2016, by Warner Bros to
generally positive reviews by critics.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.